{
    "subject": "resource/Pazuzu_(The_Exorcist)",
    "predicate": "ontology/portrayer",
    "object": "resource/Colleen_Dewhurst",
    "human_readable": "Pazuzu was portrayed by Colleen Dewhurst.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8922333121299744,
            "question": "Who portrayed Pazuzu?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7856079936027527,
            "question": "What role did Colleen Dewhurst play?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7000303864479065,
            "question": "Can you name any other roles played by Colleen Dewhurst?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6898748874664307,
            "question": "Are there any famous actors who have played Pazuzu?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6881990432739258,
            "question": "Was Colleen Dewhurst a well-known actress?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5600621700286865,
            "question": "What is Pazuzu known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5488126277923584,
            "question": "Is Pazuzu a character from a movie or play?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42688092589378357,
            "question": "What are some characteristics of the character Pazuzu?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3501654267311096,
            "question": "Has Colleen Dewhurst won any awards for her acting?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.27326586842536926,
            "question": "In what type of story or media is Pazuzu featured?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Pazuzu was portrayed by Colleen Dewhurst.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8684_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has Colleen Dewhurst won any awards for her acting?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8684_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some characteristics of the character Pazuzu?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8684_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Pazuzu a character from a movie or play?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8684_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8684_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8684_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8684_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8684_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8684_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8684_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8684_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8684_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8684_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8684_81.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response:\n\n{\n    \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n\nThis is because the documents state that \"Pazuzu's face was portrayed by Eileen Dietz\", but not by Colleen Dewhurst."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: According to the provided context, Colleen Dewhurst voiced Pazuzu for the film \"Exorcist: Legion.\" Eileen Dietz is mentioned as portraying Pazuzu's face in the original book and film. Therefore, the statement that Pazuzu was portrayed by Colleen Dewhurst is not supported by the documents."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": true,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'}\n\nThe document mentions that Colleen Dewhurst provided the voice for Pazuzu in \"Exorcist: Legion,\" but it does not state that she portrayed Pazuzu's face or appearance. The face of Pazuzu was portrayed by Eileen Dietz according to the information given."
        },
        "llama3.1:70b": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'}"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": -1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "There are multiple sources stating that Pazuzu's face was portrayed by Eileen Dietz, not Colleen Dewhurst.",
            "category": -1
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context information clearly states that Colleen Dewhurst voiced Pazuzu in \"Exorcist: Legion\", not portraying Pazuzu.",
            "category": -1
        }
    }
}